(Leonard:)Can we get an order of dumplings,
but with three instead of four?
(Waiter:)No substitutions.
(Leonard:)This isn't a substitution.
It's a reduction.
(Waiter:)Okay. No reductions.
(Leonard:)Fine. Bring us three orders of dumplings.
- That's 12, we'll each have four.
- That works.
(Sheldon:)If we fill up on dumplings,
we need to eliminate an entrée.
(Waiter:)No eliminations.
(Leonard:)If we have extra,
we'll just take the leftovers home.
And divide it how? I'm telling you,
we cannot do this without Wolowitz.
Wolowitz is with his girlfriend.
If you'd let me invite Penny,
you would've had your fourth.
Have you seen Penny eat Chinese food?
(Sheldon:)She uses a fork
and she double-dips her egg rolls.
- We don't order egg rolls.
- Exactly. But we'd have to if she was here.
Can we please make a decision?
(Raj:)Not only are there children starving in
India, there's an Indian starving right here.
There's an idea.
Why don't we go out for Indian food?
Oh, ew.
You're nice boys.
(Waiter:)Tell you what I'm going to do.
I'm gonna bring you the four dumplings.
(Waiter:)When I'm walking over to the table...